Hillman, Sidney Memorial Conference Tapes and Related Documents 5987 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sidney Hillman Memorial Conference Tapes and Related Documents
1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (University of Illinois)
5987 AV
2.22 cubic feet
2.2 linear ft.
Records (documents), audiovisual materials.
This collection is made up of tapes and related documents.
5745667
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 24, 2019
Scope and Contents
Copies were made of the original tapes.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4073: James O. Morris Office Files /4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4226: Gerd Korman Files /4256: ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials 5001 mf: American Association for Labor Legislation Records on Microfilm 5285 mf: ACWA Rochester Joint Board Scrapbooks on Microfilm 5296m: Joseph Schlossberg Diaries Excerpts 5418 mf: Committee for Industrial Organizations Minutes on Microfilm 5545: National Institute of Labor Education (NILE) Papers 5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF) 5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 5584: National Archives and Records Service Copies of Federal Documentation on Black Workers 5607: Keppele Hall Papers 5619: ACWA Records 5619 AV: ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials 5619 F: ACTWU Motion Picture Films 5619 G: ACTWU Graphics 5619 MB: ACTWU Memorabilia Collection 5619 mf: ACWA Records Parts 1-3 on Microfilm 5619 OH: ACWA Oral History Project Records 5619 P: ACTWU Photographs 5619 PUBS: ACTWU Publications 5619/002: ACWA Education Department Records 5619/003: ACWA Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks 5619/004: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/005: ACWA Bessie Hillman Papers 5619/006: ACTWU Executive Vice-President's Office Files 5619/006: ACTWU Executive Vice-President's Office Files
Hillman, Sidney, 1887-1946; Rosen, Stanley; Illinois Humanities Council; Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (University of Illinois)
5745667
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 1, 1 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 2, 2 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 3, 3 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 4, 4 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 5, 5 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 6, 6 (Box 1)
- Steve Fraser Voice, 7 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 1, 8 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 2, 9 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 3, 10 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 4, 11 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 5, 12 (Box 1)
- Sidney Hillman Conference: 6/26/1989 -- tape 6, 13 (Box 1)
- Steve Fraser Voice, 14 (Box 1)
- Hillman Lecture: 10/1989 -- tape 1, 1 (Box 2)
- Hillman Lecture: 10/1989 -- tape 2, 2 (Box 2)
- Hillman Lecture: 10/1989 -- tape 3, 3 (Box 2)
- Hillman Lecture: 10/1989 -- tape 4, 4 (Box 2)
- Hillman Lecture: 10/1989 -- tape 5, 5 (Box 2)
- Intro (Stan Rosen) Esther Peterson: Hillman Lecture 10/1989, 6 (Box 2)
- Esther Peterson: Hillman Lecture 10/1989, 7 (Box 2)
- Esther Peterson, Lynn Weiner, Sol Brandzel: Hillman Lecture 10/1989, 8 (Box 2)
- Arthur Hoover, Lawrence Levine, David Nicolai: Hillman Lecture 10/1989, 9 (Box 2)
- Discussion: Hillman Lecture -- Conclusion (Stan Rosen) 10/1989, 10 (Box 2)
- Sidney Hillman (Steve Fraser-Original) (Box 3)
- S. Fraser (Box 4)